aylien.com 2019-01-18

# Privacy Policy | AYLIEN

### Introduction

At Aylien (“Aylien”, “we”) we understand you care about data privacy and how your personal information is used and shared by us. We have created this privacy policy (“privacy policy”) to show we are commitment to protecting and safeguarding the privacy of the users (“users”, “customers”, “you”, “your”) of the services (“services”, “service”, “Aylien Services”) we provide.

### What information do we collect?

As part of the service we offer we gather a range of user data as explained below.

#### **Cookies and website tracking data**

At Aylien we use cookies, tags and scripts to track usage activity on our website (“website activity”). This website activity data is used by Aylien to improve the end user experience on our websites and to report internally on user activity on our site.

Our users are free to opt-out of cookie tracking, however, if you do so it may alter the experience of using our website and/or services we provide.

The information we gather as website activity and report on will not contain any Personally Identifiable Information (“personal information”).

##### **Personally Identifiable Information (PII)**

In some situations we will collected personal information from our users, such as names, emails, company names and credit card information, usually through signup and registration forms.

### Information sharing and storing

Personal information will never be sold or rented to third parties but it may be shared in certain circumstances as outlined below:

With trusted third parties – We may share information with our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted business partners (“partners”) for the purpose of processing personal information or Analyzed Data on our behalf. These Partners will only use the information to carry out specific business obligations to Aylien which focuses on providing our service, these Partners are bound to uphold the same standards of security and confidentiality that we have set forth in this privacy policy.

In protection of Aylien and others – We reserve the right to share or access your information when necessary to protect the rights and property of Aylien or in compliance with law or a court order.

#### **Changes to this policy**

From time to time this privacy policy may be amended in accordance with how we manage our users personal information.

#### **Contact**

If you have any concerns or questions regarding our privacy policy please don’t hesitate to contact us. Please email [hello@aylien.com](mailto:hello@aylien.com) with your query or question.

### Data Security and retention

At Aylien we take every precaution possible to protect the security of our Users and Customers information. We use SSL encrypted technology to protect the transfer of data and personal information. We store any personal information on secure servers and use state of the art, industry standard protections and procedures to ensure the safety of such information. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted via our service, during transfer and once it has been received.

While we take every precaution possible, the nature of the internet and our business means we cannot guarantee that all information stored on or transmitted to or from or servers will be free from unauthorized access. By using the Aylien Services you acknowledge that you understand and agree to the risks involved.

#### **Retention**

Private input text that is submitted by users to the API is not stored or persisted by Aylien. As part of the service we deliver, however, we do store URLs that are submitted for analysis by users. These URLs are anonymized to ensure there is no association between users and URLs submitted.

For internal purposes we do track high-level usage stats (“usage stats”) which are necessary for service monitoring and customer billing. These usage stats include features used, number of calls made and SDKs/programming languages used by our users.

#### **Hosting providers**

As is common practice for SaaS providers we partner with hosting providers from whom we lease servers. At Aylien we work with tier 1 hosting providers only, including and not limited to Amazon Web Services, Microsoft Azure, Google Cloud Platform and Digital Ocean.

#### **Secure access and transfer of data**

Access to Aylien servers and the transfer of data to and from Aylien servers is over a SSL encrypted connection.
